Victor David Software Developer

• Lagos, Nigeria

✓ vad.inc8@gmail.com

+234 9072045997

▶ https://vaad.netlify.app/



PROFILE

I'm a professional task solving Software Developer from Nigeria. I deliver quality and amazing solutions, with high and proficient skills required.

I'm well versed in team collaboration to formulate and conceptualize corporate web presence. Specialty embracing challenging projects requiring detailed coding changes, search engine-related considerations and security. Integrates knowledge of visual arts to develop functional, appealing, custom-made web products and services.

Building & Designing Software Applications with great user experience is also my expertise.

CONTACT

LinkedIn 🗗

Github 🛮

WhatsApp ♂

Twitter ☑

INTERESTS

Coding, Music, Football, Tech research

SKILLS

Frameworks/libraries:

Vue-CLI, Laravel, NodeJs, JQuery, Vuetify, Firebase, Ajax, Bootstrap, ExpressJs, NuxtJs

Infrastructure/Databases:

Php, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Mongo dB, Firestore.

Programming Languages:

JavaScript, Typescript, Python, C++, Java.

Automation / Tooling:

Git, Docker, Kubernetes., Azure, Gitlab-ci, Circle-ci.

Data Science:

Python (Data Aggregation, Data Manipulation, Data Visualization).

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering (B.Eng),

Federal University Oye-Ekiti ☑ 2019 – 2023 | Ekiti, Nigeria

Certificate degree in software development, SQI ICT ☑ 2019 – 2021 | Oyo, Nigeria

Certificate degree in ICT, SQI ICT $\ \ \, \Box$

2017 - 2019 | Oyo, Nigeria

High School (FEGO) ☑

2011 - 2017 | Oyo, Nigeria

Victor David 1 / 2

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern, Tecklink

Apr 2022 - present | Tbilisi, Georgia

- » Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Html,JavaScript,JAX and JSON Coding.
- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface
- » Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

Software Engineer, DSC

Apr 2019 - Feb 2021 | Ekiti, Nigeria

- » Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- » Trained and managed team of developers and discussed issuesin order to provide resolution and apply best practices

Web developer Intern, SQI ICT

Sep 2017 - Jan 2019 | Oyo, Nigeria

- » Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Html,JavaScript,JAX and JSON Coding.
- »Built some great projects like Banking Applications, PWA Chat Applications, Management System for Schools and Churches using Web technologieslike Php, AJAX, MySQL
- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface

PROJECTS

FuoyeMarket,

connect with your choice sellers. ☑ An Ecommerce website for connecting campus students with their choice sellers

The mightgain 🛮

It's a web application software for providing all social media services

Speedyfame 2

A web application software for improving and promoting sales through the social media.

Github 🛮

Other projects available here on github:

- Web bank applications
- Php Web chat application
- Data visualization using python
- Web E-commerce software application.
- C+ Solutions

BSF г₹

A creative website design for students organization

Victor David 2 / 2